<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android UI</string>
    <string name="assignment">In this assignment you need to make an app that has 5 different activities. The main activity is a list of buttons, each of which will launch a new activity within the app.

Each of those activities should display at least 5 elements in a different way. The elements can be entirely at your choosing.

A minimal example that fully meets the requirements would be displaying the numbers 1 through 5 in a LinearLayout (horizontal and vertical), a GridLayout and a RelativeLayout.

Alternatively you could replace one or more of those with Views bound to Adapters if you wanted to get a little more advanced with your implementation. For example you could use a RecyclerView to display a infinite list of numbers.

Deliverables:

You should zip up the entire project directory and submit it as a zip file (you should not include the directories created by building, we just want the source code). You should also record a video demonstrating the functionality of your project. This can be uploaded to media.oregonstate.edu and a link to the video submitted as a comment along with the assignment.

Previous Next
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grid_layout">Grid Layout Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_linear_layout">Linear Layout Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_assignment">Assignment Activity</string>
    <string name="tab_1_text">Text to display when the first tab is selected</string>
    <string name="tab_2_text">Text to display when the second is selected</string>
    <string name="tab_3_text">Text to display when the third tab is selected.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed_layout">Tabbed Layout Activity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">I Could make this do stuff</string>
    <string name="linear_layout_button_text">Linear Layout</string>
    <string name="grid_layout_button_Text">Grid Layout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_table_layout">Table Layout</string>
</resources>
